<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>漢黨 Han Party</title>
    <link>https://hanparty.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on 漢黨 Han Party</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2020 漢黨 Han Party</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2021 10:58:17 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://hanparty.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Yellow calendar</title>
      <link>https://hanparty.github.io/articles/huangli/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2021 10:58:17 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hanparty.github.io/articles/huangli/</guid>
      <description>The Yellow calendar, that is, the Yellow Emperor calendar, is a traditional Chinese calendar. It is the ancient six calendars with the Xia calendar, Yin calendar, Zhou calendar, Lu calendar and Zhuanxu calendar. According to a large number of historical records, it was made after Emperor Huang broke Chiyou. It is said that the calendar year began from the day when the yellow emperor ascended the throne. Xuanyuan Yellow Emperor was the cultural ancestor of Huayi, and was the same ancestor of Huayi with Shennong Yan Emperor, Dongyi people and Chiyou of Miao people (there are three ancestral halls of China in Zhuolu, Hebei).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xiaosui </title>
      <link>https://hanparty.github.io/posts/xiaosui/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 09:43:28 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hanparty.github.io/posts/xiaosui/</guid>
      <description>Today&amp;rsquo;s Xiaosui is on the 23rd day of the twelfth lunar month. At this point, every household is hygienic and has a good year&amp;rsquo;s taste. After Xiaosui, it&amp;rsquo;s new year. Xiaosui is a dress rehearsal on the first day of the lunar calendar. It&amp;rsquo;s a beautiful wish for Chinese people to say goodbye to the old and welcome the new.
There are kitchen king, window decoration, Spring Festival couplets, dust cleaning, marriage, eating sesame candy and dumplings in the small age customs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Communication</title>
      <link>https://hanparty.github.io/communication/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2021 10:37:28 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hanparty.github.io/communication/</guid>
      <description>We welcome those with lofty ideals into our community
Please abide by the law, civilized exchanges
https://discord.gg/7N8EYQGMwN</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Han Party</title>
      <link>https://hanparty.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hanparty.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Han Party, is the Party of the han people, is to make Chinese welfare.
Study the Han culture, carry forward the Han civilization, rejuvenation of China, the Great Han Dynasty.
This is the highest pursuit of the Han Party.
More details:
official website of HanParty</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
